# **LITIET** Bio-inspired Microsystems Laboratory

Type your keywords... Search

Publications Lectures Fun Notice Contact	Lectures	Publications	Research	Members	About Us	Home
--	----------	--------------	----------	---------	----------	------

### Members

### **Professor**



### Seong-Jin Kim

School of Electrical and Computer Engineering EB3(106) #401-1, UNIST 50 UNIST-gil, Eonyang-eup, Ulju-gun, Ulsan South Korea, 44919

Phone: +82-52-217-2115 Email: kimsj at unist.ac.kr

### Summary

Seong-Jin Kim received his B.S. degree in Electrical Engineering from Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH), Pohang, Korea, in 2001. He received his M.S. and Ph.D. degree in Electrical Engineering from Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), Daejeon, Korea, in 2003 and 2008, respectively.

From 2008 to 2012, he was a research staff member at Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT) in Yongin, Korea, where he engaged in the development of CMOS imager for real-time acquisition of 3-D images. From 2012 to 2015, he worked for Institute of Microelectronics (IME), A\*STAR in Singapore, where he was involved in the design of analog-mixed signal circuits for various sensing systems. In 2015, he joined the School of Electrical and Computer Engineering at Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST) in South Korea as an Assistant Professor. His current research interests include high performance imaging devices, and biomedical interface circuits and systems.

### Education

Mar. 2003 – Feb. 2008 Ph.D in Dept. of Electrical Engineering at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)
Mar. 2001 – Feb. 2003 MS in Dept. of Electrical Engineering at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)
Mar. 1997 – Feb. 2001 BS in Dept. of Electrical Engineering at Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH)
Mar. 1994 – Feb. 1997 Hansung Science High School

### • Professional Experience

Jul. 2015 – Present Assistant Professor in School of Electrical and Computer Engineering at Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST) Jun. 2012 – Jun. 2015 Scientist II (Senior Research Staff) in Institute of Microelectronics (IME), A\*STAR, Singapore Jan. 2008 – May. 2012 Research Staff in Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT, 삼성종합기술원)
Sep. 2006 – Nov. 2007 Pre-doctoral Researcher in Department of Electrical Engineering and Computer at the University of Minnesota, Twin Cities

### **Graduate Students**



### Bumjun Kim

MS Candidate from 2016. 9 BS in ECE from UNIST in 2016. 8

Research Topic: CMOS image sensor for LiDAR Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: tigerjun at unist.ac.kr



### Seunghyun Lee

MS Candidate from 2017. 3
BS in ECE from UNIST in 2017. 2

Research Topic: CMOS image sensor for LiDAR Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: Ish8482 at unist.ac.kr

### Yongtae Shin

MS Candidate from 2018. 3 BS in ECE from UNIST in 2018. 2



Research Topic: Low power oscillator Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: syt9271 at unist.ac.kr



Jeeho Park

MS Candidate from 2018. 3 BS in ECE from UNIST in 2018. 2

Research Topic: Low power oscillator Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: jeeho12 at unist.ac.kr



Sanguk Lee

MS Candidate from 2018. 3 BS in ECE from UNIST in 2018. 2

Research Topic: CMOS image sensor Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: better19kr at unist.ac.kr



Jihyoung Cha

MS Candidate from 2018. 3 BS in ECE from UNIST in 2018. 2

Research Topic: CMOS biosensors Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: cyo9577 at unist.ac.kr



Suhyun Han

MS Candidate from 2018. 3 BS in BE and ECE from UNIST in 2018. 2

Research Topic: Implantable neural recording IC Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: gkstngus1456 at naver.com

## **Undergraduate Students**

### Yongjae Park

Senior in UNIST

Research Topic: Implantable neural recording IC Office: EB3(106) #507 Email: conuum at unist.ac.kr

### **Changyong Shin**

Senior in UNIST

Research Topic: CMOS image sensor Office: EB3(106) #507

Email: dokdo at unist.ac.kr

Copyright©UNIST BiML. All Rights Reserved.